<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorial on</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorial on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Python &amp; Neovim</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/python-neovim/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 19:37:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/python-neovim/</guid><description>language &amp;amp; text editor
What do you need to have? # Hej, today we begin learning with Nutek to be able to use it how I see it fit. First be sure you have one of the following:
neosb/nutek-core:0.4.0 from Docker Hub Nutek from crates.io or Github - working on a fix You could follow on with Python3, pip, venv and Neovim What you will learn? # I want to show you few Python use cases and how to write code in Neovim.</description></item><item><title>Python3. Filling the Tank</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/python3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 14:28:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/python3/</guid><description>⛽️ for our rocket 🚀
Ground-up # In previous post I tried to show you how to write simple program in neovim and run using python3. Today I want to fill in the gaps in your knowledge of my understanding of how developer work. First of all we will touch on some Vim commands that migh be useful and then we&amp;rsquo;ll build a tool that show where International Space Station is and who is currently in space.</description></item><item><title>Hugo. My First Website</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/hugo/</guid><description>Create YOUR first website # Hej!
This New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve you have so many new resolutions that you need to get them into one place, and make them public, so you can be as transparent as your nearest politician is.
So you heard that there is GitHub, Nutek, Szymon, Hugo and whoever I have to mention to make you test this, because it&amp;rsquo;s so awesome to have your own static website build with Hugo Markdown and all crazy stuff.</description></item><item><title>🦀 Learn Rust</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/learn-rust/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 21:16:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/learn-rust/</guid><description>Book about Rust programming # Do you want to learn about new competitor to C? Do you want to write safe and fast code? Do you want to join large community of agile developers tackling almost any challange there is, even games? Do you want to learn a new language? Do you want to know what AI is capable of? Go to learn-rust and start yours Tour de Rust now!</description></item><item><title>🛤 Learn C</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/learn-c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:24:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/learn-c/</guid><description>learn-c # My code while learning C and some data for you # Szymon Bronisław Błaszczyński © 2023 museyoucoulduse@gmail.com
For those seeking peace at time of war, and those at war in time of peace.
Powered by https://cj.rs/riss
first-one # Overview # This program greets my cat in many colors. The trick used here is simple, you take number 31, which stands for red, and iterates until 37, meaning it will never hit 38, thus i &amp;lt; 38.</description></item><item><title>C Encrypt Decrypt</title><link>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/c-encrypt-decrypt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:33:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nutek.neosb.net/docs/tutorial/c-encrypt-decrypt/</guid><description>-fu with C language
I never really liked C or C++, but we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on C. This article is about how big trouble is to get things done when you have limited resources available on the web, and only one friend - ChatGPT.
Idea # I want to easily encrypt and decrypt a message. May it be a file, may it be a string. I wan&amp;rsquo;t to hide it from general public.</description></item></channel></rss>